

Akhmetzhanov **Ravil** ML/CV engineer

- & Universitetskaya 1, Innopolis, Russia
- ☑ akhm.ravil99@gmail.com
- **©** +79833430859

SOCIAL

- in Ravil Akhmetzhanov
- navil99
- **◄** @Ravilek

PROFILE

Master Student in Innopolis University.

I am interested in Computer Vision, Machine and Deep Learning.

I have strong engineering and mathematical background along with experience of working in the industry

I enjoy networking and public speaking. Part of Innopolis Stand Up comedy club.

HARD SKILLS

- Python, JavaScript
- ML/CV and statistics
- Pandas, Sklearn, PyTorch
- OpenCV
- Linux, Docker

- TensorRT
- Flask on backend
- HTML, CSS, Svelte on frontend
- Electronics
- Verilog HDL

EXPERIENCE

FPGA Intern

Jun 2019 - October 2019 | Micran, Tomsk, full-time Project - 4 port 1 Gb/s Ethernet Switch on Verilog HDL. Altera Cyclone V FPGA was used.

Computer Vision Engineer

Feb 2022 - Current time | Techtrans, St. Petersburg, remote, part-time

Completed various CV tasks: dataset preparation, training and evaluation of Deep Learning models, deployment on different embedded devices.

Contributed to several software project from back(Flask) and frontend(Svelte) sides. Company projects are dedicated to railway security.

REWARDS

Russian State Higher Scholarship (2019)

• For academic achievements. Scholarship for 2019 Autumn Semester.

Micran Company Scholarship (2021)

• For academic achievements. Scholarship for 2021 Spring Semester.

AkBars Bank Scholarship (2022)

• For academic achievements. Scholarship for 2022-2023 Academic Year.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree. Electronics and Nanoelectronics.

Tomsk Polytechnic University

2016 - 2021

GPA: 4.8/5

Master's degree. Computer Science: "Robotics and Computer Vision" track.

Innopolis University

2021 - 2023

GPA: 4.9/5

LANGUAGES

Russian - Native

English - C1Kazakh - B1

INTERESTS

①

Movies

Football Cooking Music